Guide to the Boniface I. Obichere papers, 1959-1996
Obichere, Boniface I. papers, 1959-1996
- Series IV. Written Works, Speeches, and Publications
  - Obichere's Works
    - "Kenneth Onwuka Dike" in ASA News, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - "King Ghezo of Dahomey, 1818-1858," unpublished, presented at the History Seminar, University of Ilorin, Nigeria, 1972, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - "Lagos" from the fifteenth edition of Encyclopedia Britannica, 1972-1974 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - "Leadership in Africa Series," editor, 1972 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - "Military Dependence in Historical Perspective: The Case of Nigeria," in The Conch, 1973 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - "Nationalism, Irredentism or Nihilism: Struggles for 'Liberation' in Post Independence Africa, 1960-1983" (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - "Nigeria: The Difficult Road Back to Civilian Rule", 1978 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - "Nigeria's Oil Refineries: Assets or Liabilities," in Alvana Journal of the Social Sciences; presented at the Conference on Science, Technology and Development, 1981 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - "The Origin and Development of the Fon Kingdom of Dahomey", unpublished, presented at the History Seminar, University of Ife, Nigeria, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - "Politicians and Educational Reform in French-Speaking West Africa: A Comparative Study of Mali and the Ivory Coast," in Journal of the Historical Society of Nigeria, 1976 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - "The 'Protest' Tradition in West Indian Poetry: From George Campbell to Martin Carter", 1972 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - "Reconstruction in Guinea-Bissau: From Revolutionaries and Guerillas to Bureaucrats and Politicians," in A Current Bibliography on African Affairs, 1975 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - "The Role of Nigeria's Oil Refineries in Her Economy" in Nigerian Forum, 1982 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - "Scramble, Partition and Conquest" in Africa Under Foreign Domination, 1880-1935, Vol.VII, Unesco's History of Africa, 1972-1975 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - "The Significance and Challenge of Afro-American Studies for Students and Faculty at the Institutions of Higher Learning in the United States" (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - "Slavery and the Slave Trade in the Niger Delta-Cross River Basin" (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - "Slavery in Asanti and Dahomey," chapter in Slavery and Servitude in Africa (did not make the book), 1973-1976 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - "The Social Character of Slavery in Asante and Dahomey" in Ufahamu, 1983 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Soldier as Citizen in Africa: The Changing Role of the Military in African Societies, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - Soldier as Citizen in Africa: Cookey, S.J.S., ca.1972 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - Soldier as Citizen in Africa: Eleazu, Uma O., ca.1972 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - Soldier as Citizen in Africa: Kilson, Martin, ca.1972 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - Soldier as Citizen in Africa: Kranzdorf, Richard, ca.1972 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Soldier as Citizen in Africa: Kuper, Hilda, ca.1972 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Soldier as Citizen in Africa: Lemarchand, René, ca.1972 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Soldier as Citizen in Africa: Lofchie, Michael F., ca.1972 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Soldier as Citizen in Africa: Luckham, Robin, ca.1972 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Soldier as Citizen in Africa: Marcus, Harold G., ca.1972 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Soldier as Citizen in Africa: Martin, Michel L., 1972 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Soldier as Citizen in Africa: Ranger, Terence, ca.1972 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Soldier as Citizen in Africa: Skinner, Elliot P., ca.1972 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Soldier as Citizen in Africa: Unknown author, ca.1972 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - Soldier as Citizen in Africa: Uzoigwe, G.N., ca.1972 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - Soldier as Citizen in Africa: Welch, Claude E., ca.1972 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - Studies in Southern Nigerian History, editor, 1972-1983 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - Studies in Southern Nigerian History: Book proof, 1978 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - Studies in Southern Nigerian History: Bibliography, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - Studies in Southern Nigerian History: Bibliography note cards, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 46-47)
    - Studies in Southern Nigerian History: Afigbo, A.E., 1971-1978 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Studies in Southern Nigerian History: Ahanotu, Austin M., 1977 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - Studies in Southern Nigerian History: Anyanwu, E. Agulanna, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - Studies in Southern Nigerian History: Asiegbu, Johnson U., ca.1977 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - Studies in Southern Nigerian History: Ayandele, E. A., 1974-1977 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Studies in Southern Nigerian History: Ekechi, Felix K. (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - Studies in Southern Nigerian History: Esedebe, Peter Olisanwuche, 1975-1977 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Studies in Southern Nigerian History: Ifemsia, C. C., 1977 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - Studies in Southern Nigerian History: Ijere, Martin O., 1977 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - Studies in Southern Nigerian History: Mbaeyi, Paul M., 1977 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - Studies in Southern Nigerian History: Noah, Monday Efiong (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - Studies in Southern Nigerian History: Ogueri, Eze II (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - Studies in Southern Nigerian History: Olusanya, G.O., 1977 (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Studies in Southern Nigerian History: Omu, Fred I.A., 1977 (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Studies in Southern Nigerian History: Onwuka, Uga, 1977 (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - "Towards the Historical Study of Oracles and Politics in West Africa", 1970 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - "The United States and Africa: From Benign Neglect to Reluctant and Hesitant Involvement", Oct. 12, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - "West Africa: A Historical Overview," in Proceedings of the West Africa Conference, edited by Patricia Paylore and Richard A. Haney, Jr., n.d. (1976) (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - West African States and European Expansion: The Dahomey-Niger Hinterland, 1885-1898, 1973 (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - West African States and European Expansion: Manuscript (I) (Box 17, Folder 7-10)
    - West African States and European Expansion: Manuscript (II), 1971 (Box 17, Folder 11-18)
    - (2) Original map drawings used in Obichere's book West African States, 1971 (Box 36)
    - "Women and Slavery in the Kingdom of Dahomey," in Revue Française d'Histoire d'Outre-Mer, 1978 (Box 17, Folder 19)
    - World Encyclopedia of Black People, 1974-1975 (Box 17, Folder 20)
    - Transcribed interview, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 21)
    - Obichere writings: Unidentified, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 22)
    - Obichere event flyers and newspaper clippings, 1968-1996 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - Other Authors' Manuscripts
    - Authors: Ad, 1976, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Authors: Af-Al, 1971-1972, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Authors: Ang, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 25-26)
    - Authors: Ani-Arh, 1972, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Authors: Ar-Az, 1970-1971, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Authors: Az, 1969, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Authors: Ba-Berg, 1976, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Authors: Bert-Bon, 1972, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Authors: Booth, 1968 (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Authors: Bou-Ca, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 32)
    - Authors: Ce-Ch, 1974, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 33)
    - Authors: Co, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 34)
    - Authors: D, 1981, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 35)
    - Authors: E, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Authors: F, 1969, 1974, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 36)
    - Authors: G, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Authors: Hal, 1974 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Authors: Har-Ij, n.d. (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Authors: Ijere, 1970 (Box 18, Folder 3-4)
    - Authors: Iw-J, 1971, 1983, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Authors: Ke, 1972, 1976 (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Authors: Kincaid, Larry, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 7-14)
    - Authors: Kl-Ko, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Authors: L, 1970, 1975, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Authors: Ma-Mb, 1978, 1986, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Authors: Me-Mor, 1972, 1976, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Authors: Mos-Mu, n.d. (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Authors: N, 1976, 1985, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 1)
    - Authors: Nair, Kannan K., 1975 (Box 18, Folder 20-21)
    - Authors: Ogbu, John U., n.d. (Box 18, Folder 22-24)
    - Authors: Ogg-Okoye, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 2)
    - Authors: Okonji, Ogbolu M., 1973 (Box 18, Folder 25)
    - Authors: Okoye, Mokwugo, 1972 (Box 18, Folder 26)
    - Authors: Okoye, Mokwugo, 1972 (Box 20, Folder 1-4)
    - Authors: Olafioye, Tayo, 1979 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Authors: Olafioye, Tayo, 1984 (Box 19, Folder 3)
    - Authors: Olo-On, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Authors: P, 1969, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Authors: Q, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Authors: Rhodes, Barbara Anthony, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 9-10)
    - Authors: Rh-Ro, 1971, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Authors: Sa-Sk, 1971, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 4)
    - Authors: Songolo, Aliko, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 12-13)
    - Authors: T, 1972, 1975, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 5)
    - Authors: Ubah, C.N., n.d. (Box 20, Folder 14-15)
    - Authors: Ub-Uc, 1978, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 6)
    - Authors: Ukpabi, S.C., n.d. (Box 20, Folder 16-17)
    - Authors: V, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Authors: W-Z, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Authors: Unknown, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 20-23)
    - Authors: Unknown, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 7)
    - Miscellaneous bibliographies, 1970-1975, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 8-9)
  - Publications
    - Pamphlets, magazines, newsletters: Af, 1967-1973 (Box 19, Folder 10)
    - Pamphlets, magazines, newsletters: Al-Ap, 1966-1982, n.d. (Box 20, Folder 24)
    - Pamphlets, magazines, newsletters: B, 1972-1994 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Pamphlets, magazines, newsletters: C, 1966-1985 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Pamphlets, magazines, newsletters: D, 1966-1975, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 11)
    - Pamphlets, magazines, newsletters: F-H, 1973-1996 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Pamphlets, magazines, newsletters: I-J, 1972-1985 (Box 19, Folder 12)
    - Pamphlets, magazines, newsletters: K-M, 1967-1992, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 13)
    - Pamphlets, magazines, newsletters: N-O, 1964-1986 (Box 19, Folder 14)
    - Pamphlets, magazines, newsletters: P-R, 1970-1988 (Box 19, Folder 15)
    - Pamphlets, magazines, newsletters: S-So, 1969-1973 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Pamphlets, magazines, newsletters: St-Su, 1978-1979 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Pamphlets, magazines, newsletters: T-U, 1973-1992, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 16)
    - Pamphlets, magazines, newsletters: V-W, 1972-1995 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Pamphlets, magazines, newsletters: X-Z, 1975-1982 (Box 19, Folder 17)
    - Annual reports: A-H, 1970-1974 (Box 19, Folder 18)
    - Annual reports: N-W, 1985-1994 (Box 19, Folder 19)
    - Reprints: Authors: A-F, 1971-1983, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Reprints: Authors: H-L, 1968-1978, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Reprints: Authors: M-N, 1969-1979 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Reprints: Authors: O-P, 1969-1989 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Reprints: Authors: S-U, 1964-1973 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Reprints: Authors: V-Z, 1965-1974 (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Newspapers, 1967-1989 (Box 22)
    - Photocopied articles: Authors: A, 1984-1985, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 20)
    - Photocopied articles: Authors: B, 1967-1974 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Photocopied articles: Authors: C, 1966-1967, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 21)
    - Photocopied articles: Authors: D-F, 1982, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Photocopied articles: Authors: G-K, 1968, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Photocopied articles: Authors: M, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Photocopied articles: Authors: N-O, 1074-1993, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 22)
    - Photocopied articles: Authors: P-S, 1974-1978, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Photocopied articles: Authors: T-Wh, 1969, 1973, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Photocopied articles: Authors: Wi-Z, 1989, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 14)
    - Photocopied articles: Authors unknown, 1969-1994, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 15)
    - Photocopied articles: Government documents: Nigeria, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 23)
    - Photocopied articles: Government documents: Uganda (Box 21, Folder 16)
    - Photocopied articles: Government documents: Zambia, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 17)
    - Newspaper clippings, 1960-1995, n.d. (Box 19, Folder 24)
    - Pamphlets, magazines, newsletters: A, misc. (Box 38, Folder 1)
    - Pamphlets, magazines, newsletters: B-D, misc. (Box 38, Folder 2)
    - Pamphlets, magazines, newsletters:E, misc. (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Ford Foundation publicaitons, misc. (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Pamphlets, magazines, newsletters: F-H, misc. (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Pamphlets, magazines, newsletters: I, misc. (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Pamphlets, magazines, newsletters: J-L, misc. (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Pamphlets, magazines, newsletters: M-P, misc. (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Pamphlets, magazines, newsletters: R, misc. (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Sudan Journal of Economic and Social Studies, misc. (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Pamphlets, magazines, newsletters: T-Y, misc. (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Instituto de Angola publication, misc. (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - University of California Los Angeles (UCLA) publications, misc. (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - UCLA African Studies newsletter, misc. (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Annales de l'Universite du Benin, 1981 (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Universite de Bordeaux publicaitons, 1973, 1985 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Documentation Legislattive Africaine from the Universite de Dakar, 1972 (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - University of Ilorin, Nigeria Calendar, 1981/1982 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - US Government Committe on Foreign Affairs hearings regarding Rhodesia, 1973, 1975 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Misc. hearing booklets of the US Governments Committee on Foreign Affairs, 1973-1975 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Highlighting the NEA's Radical Political Agenda: Who's Ruining Our Schools?, 1988 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Perpétue et l'habitude du malheur, by Mong Beti, 1974 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Report on the Supply of Secondary Level Teachers in English-Speaking Africa, Nigeria, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Report on the Supply of Secondary Level Teachers in English-Speaking Africa, summary, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Sociology Post-Graduates of South African Universities, by Hansi P. Pollak, 1969 (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Conference Materials
    - African Studies Association Annual meetings, 1969-1971 (Box 21, Folder 18)
    - African Studies Association Annual meetings, 1974, 1975, 1982 (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - African Studies Association Annual meetings, 1984, 1985, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Africanist Cooperation in Afro-American Programs, 1969 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - American Historical Association Annual meetings, 1972-1973 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Association of African Historians, 2nd Ordinary Congress, 1975 (Box 19, Folder 25)
    - Berlin West Africa Conference, 1985 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - 5th International Congress of African Studies, 1985 (Box 19, Folder 26-27)
    - Phelps-Stokes Seminar on African-American Relations, 1974 (Box 21, Folder 24-25)
    - Conferences, 1968-1969 (Box 19, Folder 28)
    - Conferences, 1970-1974 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Conferences, 1975-1978 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Conferences, 1983-1990 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Conferences, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - African Studies Association Annual Meeting Booklets, 1971, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Communications au Colloque- Universite de Nantes, résumés, 1985 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - International Conference on the UNity of the Sciences report, 1987 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - 9th International Congress of Anthropological and Ethnological Sciences, 1973 (Box 39, Folder 12)
- Series V. Journal of African Studies
  - General
    - Guidelines and descriptions, 1987-1988, n.d. (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Flyers, 1974-1982, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Mailing list, Feb. 28, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Correspondence, 1969-1974 (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, 1975 (Box 4, Folder 34)
    - Correspondence, 1976-1979 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence, 1981-1994 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Submissions
    - Submissions: Acam-Oturu, Assumpta, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Submissions: Adebayo, A.G., 1989-1990 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Submissions: Adeoye, A.O., 1988 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Submissions: Adjaye, Joseph K., 1984 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - Submissions: Afolayan, Michael Oladejo, 1983 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Submissions: Ahanotu, Austin, 1976 (Box 21, Folder 34)
    - Submissions: Aja, Egbeke, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 35)
    - Submissions: Ajulo, Sunday Babalola, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Submissions: Akinsanya, Adeoye and Rotimi Ajayi, 1983, 1989-1992 (Box 21, Folder 36)
    - Submissions: Akong'a, Joshua, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 37)
    - Submissions: Ampiah, Kweku, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 38)
    - Submissions: Anyanwu, U.D., 1987 (Box 21, Folder 39)
    - Submissions: Arifalo, S.O., 1984 (Box 21, Folder 40)
    - Submissions: Atemie, Josiah D., 1983 (Box 21, Folder 41)
    - Submissions: Awotokun, A.M., 1995 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Submissions: Bishop, Rand, 1987 (Box 21, Folder 42)
    - Submissions: Boafo-Arthur, Kwame, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 43)
    - Submissions: Bodunde, Charles, 1990 (Box 21, Folder 44)
    - Submissions: Busari, Adekunle Alade, n.d. (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Submissions: Chikeka, Charles O., 1983 (Box 21, Folder 45)
    - Submissions: Chikulo, B.C., 1984 (Box 21, Folder 46)
    - Submissions: Cownie, David S., 1984 (Box 21, Folder 47)
    - Submissions: Curry, Robert L. Jr., 1986 (Box 21, Folder 48)
    - Submissions: Danfulani, Shuaibu Ahmed, 1992 (Box 21, Folder 49)
    - Submissions: Dei, George J.S., 1988 (Box 21, Folder 50)
    - Submissions: Deku, Afrikadzata, 1995 (Box 21, Folder 51)
    - Submissions: Diallo, Alimou and J.H. Landi, 1991 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Submissions: Ebigbola, Joshua A., 1983 (Box 21, Folder 52)
    - Submissions: Ejizu, Christopher I., 1987 (Box 21, Folder 53)
    - Submissions: Ekiyor, Henry A., 1987 (Box 21, Folder 54)
    - Submissions: Ekoko, Edhe, 1979 (Box 23, Folder 9)
    - Submissions: Emezi, C.E., 1975 (Box 23, Folder 10)
    - Submissions: Enworom, Agubade S., 1984 (Box 23, Folder 11)
    - Submissions: Evuleocha, Stevina U., 1988 (Box 21, Folder 55)
    - Submissions: Eze, Nwagbo, 1988 (Box 21, Folder 56)
    - Submissions: Fawole, W. Alade, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Submissions: Felleke, Getachew, 1996 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Submissions: Ghatpande, S.M., 1982 (Box 23, Folder 12)
    - Submissions: Grey, Mark A., 1989 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Submissions: Hailu, Alem, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Submissions: Harris, Mitchell J., 1987 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - Submissions: Holbrook, Wendell P. (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - Submissions: Holloway, Joseph E., ca. 1979 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - Submissions: Ibikunle, Tijani Hakeem, 1989 (Box 23, Folder 13)
    - Submissions: Iheakaram, P.O., 1980-1982 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - Submissions: Imaga, Emmanuel U.L., 1988 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - Submissions: Imobighe, T.A., 1979, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - Submissions: Isabirye, Stephen B., 1988 (Box 23, Folder 14)
    - Submissions: Iweriebor, Ehiedu E.G., 1983, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - Submissions: James, Ibrahim, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Submissions: Kelley, Michael A., 1987 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Submissions: Kieh, George Klay, Jr., 1987 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Submissions: Kilson, Marion, 1978-1979 (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Submissions: Konde, Emmanuel, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Submissions: Kuranga, Abraham A., 1993 (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Submissions: Lawuyi, O.B., 1992 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Submissions: Liviga, Athumani, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Submissions: Lo, Andre and Carla Livingstone, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 20)
    - Submissions: Lofchie, Michael F., 1981 (Box 23, Folder 15)
    - Submissions: Lombardi, Mark Owen, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 21)
    - Submissions: Mawela, Mondonga Mokoli, 1987-1988 (Box 24, Folder 22)
    - Submissions: Mensah, A.H.O., 1984 (Box 23, Folder 16)
    - Submissions: Mohtadi, Shahruz, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 23)
    - Submissions: Mojuetan, B.A., 1995 (Box 24, Folder 24)
    - Submissions: Mufune, Pempelani, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 25)
    - Submissions: Mwase, Ngila, 1984, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 26)
    - Submissions: Ndlovu, Callistus, 1975 (Box 24, Folder 27)
    - Submissions: Nelson, Carlos I.H., 1984 (Box 24, Folder 28)
    - Submissions: Nji, Ajaga, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 29)
    - Submissions: Nkrumah, Gorkey Gamal, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 30)
    - Submissions: Nwabueze, P. Emeka, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 31)
    - Submissions: Nwabughuogu, Anthony I., 1983 (Box 23, Folder 17)
    - Submissions: Nwachukwu-Agbada, J.O.J., 1988 (Box 24, Folder 32)
    - Submissions: Nwaka, Geoffrey I., 1978 (Box 24, Folder 33)
    - Submissions: Nwoye, Augustine, 1987 (Box 23, Folder 18)
    - Submissions: Obi, Joseph E., 1988 (Box 24, Folder 34)
    - Submissions: Obidi, S.S., 1986 (Box 24, Folder 35)
    - Submissions: Odesola, Segun Nathaniel, 1987-1989 (Box 24, Folder 36)
    - Submissions: Ohaegbulam, F. Ugboaja, 1983, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 37)
    - Submissions: Okafor, F.O.E., 1990 (Box 24, Folder 38)
    - Submissions: Okonkwo, Chuka Eze, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 39)
    - Submissions: Okonkwo, Valentine, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 40)
    - Submissions: Okoye, J.C., 1989 (Box 24, Folder 41)
    - Submissions: Oladeji, Niyi, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 42)
    - Submissions: Olaoba, O.B., 1995 (Box 24, Folder 43)
    - Submissions: Olugbade, Kola, n.d. (Box 24, Folder 44)
    - Submissions: Olukoju, Ayodeji, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 45)
    - Submissions: Onyeledo, Godwin-Collins, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 46)
    - Submissions: Onyewuenyi, Innocent C., 1983 (Box 24, Folder 47)
    - Submissions: Opeola, S. Modupeola, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 48)
    - Submissions: Orobator, S.E., 1984, 1995 (Box 23, Folder 19)
    - Submissions: Oshin, V.O., 1988 (Box 23, Folder 20)
    - Submissions: Osia, Kunirum, 1989-1990 (Box 24, Folder 49)
    - Submissions: Osikoya, Tope W., 1987 (Box 24, Folder 50)
    - Submissions: Owoeye, Jide, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 51)
    - Submissions: Oyeleye, D.A., 1991 (Box 24, Folder 52)
    - Submissions: Prouty, Chris, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 53)
    - Submissions: Reitano, Richard and Peter Volpe, 1992 (Box 24, Folder 54)
    - Submissions: Rich, Paul B., 1983 (Box 24, Folder 55)
    - Submissions: Roberts, George O., 1979 (Box 24, Folder 56)
    - Submissions: Roberts, Sheila, 1983 (Box 24, Folder 57)
    - Submissions: Rotimi, Bunni O., 1979 (Box 24, Folder 58)
    - Submissions: Saha, Santosh C., 1993 (Box 24, Folder 59)
    - Submissions: Sarfo, Kwasi, 1989 (Box 24, Folder 60)
    - Submissions: Sekgoma, Gilbert A., 1989 (Box 24, Folder 61)
    - Submissions: Shettima, Kole Ahmed, 1991 (Box 24, Folder 62)
    - Submissions: Shitu-Agbetola, Ade, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 63)
    - Submissions: Sholanke, Oladipo O., 1992 (Box 23, Folder 21)
    - Submissions: Shyllon, Folarin, 1978 (Box 24, Folder 64)
    - Submissions: Sturn, Alicia Marie, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 65)
    - Submissions: Suberu, Rotimi Timothy, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 66)
    - Submissions: Sultan, Alfonzie Hakim, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 67)
    - Submissions: Talhami, Ghada, 1984 (Box 24, Folder 68)
    - Submissions: Taylor, Kenwyn, 1990 (Box 24, Folder 69)
    - Submissions: Tembo, Mwizenge S., n.d. (Box 24, Folder 70)
    - Submissions: Ubah, C.N., 1974 (Box 24, Folder 71)
    - Submissions: Uwatt, Effiok B., 1991 (Box 24, Folder 72)
    - Submissions: Waters, Harold A., 1987 (Box 24, Folder 73)
    - Submissions: Weiner, Daniel and Sam Moyo, 1987 (Box 24, Folder 74)
    - Submissions: Younge, Gavin, 1988 (Box 24, Folder 75)
  - Journal of African Studies
    - Journal of African Studies, Vol.4, Nos.1, 3, 1977 (Box 24, Folder 76)
    - Journal of African Studies, Vol.6, Nos.2-4, 1979-1980 (Box 24, Folder 77)